# AMAR SINGH JADON

PROJECT MANAGER

Jaipur, Raj +91-9784592887 amar.jadon@gmail.com http://phpinfo.in/resume

Hi, I've more than 9 years of experience in Web development industry and from last 5 years I am working as a Project Manager. I am expert in end-to-end implementation of the SDLC including implementation of specifications, design, development, implementation, quality of Product etc. I am also proficient at grasping new technical concepts quickly and utilizing the same in a productive manner.

EXPERIENCE

ITRevoluci, Bikaner, Raj

http://www.itrevoluci.com/

Dec. 2015 - Present

Project Manager / Business Analyst, Owner

Responsible for getting projects from freelancing platforms and after that need to manage everything till final delivery.

Netleon Technologies Pvt Ltd., Jaipur, Raj

Oct. 2010 - Dec. 2015

http://www.netleon.com/

Project Manager

I was responsible for everything from analysis to delivery. It included Project analysis, requirements gathering, implementation, testing, delivery etc.

Dotsquares Technologies, Jaipur, Raj

Nov. 2008 - Oct. 2010

http://www.dotsquares.com/

Sr. S/W Engineer

I was involved in web development using different frameworks and CMS as desired by clients and at the same time created bonding in team so they can perform their roles effectively.

smartData Enterprises, Nagpur, Maharashtra

Feb. 2008 - Oct. 2008

http://www.smartdatainc.com/

Software Engineer

This is the company where I learned a lot of things. Here I worked on a live project related to realestate domain. I integrated MLS listing and almost all the features in that site. At that time there was not any readymade CMS like wordpress so we created all the things from scratch and that's why I learned so much here.

Sonik Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Bikaner, Raj

May. 2007 - Feb. 2008

http://www.soniktechnologies.in/

Software Trainee

Here I joined as a .Net trainee but later on switched to PHP. First 3 months was a training and then worked on inhouse projects.

PORTFOLIO

### Milestone Projects

#### RGAVP

We created this project for Rajasthan Grameen Aajeevika Vikas Parishad department of Rajasthan Govt. It's a milestone project in my project management career. As project was related to Raj Govt so there was not any scope of error and it was very difficult to get requirements from Govt people but in the end we completed this successfully. Apart from the website we created MIS, from where management people can view the reports and all the information. This MIS system gets the data from all the SHG's of rajasthan state.

http://rgavp.org

StirUP

It's a gift sharing app & website which we created. In this I was taking care the website and API management for mobile app.

https://www.stirup.co/

Paydirtgold

This project is also a key project for me as it was in shopify and we did a lot of customization in this. I also cusomized some of sections at myself as I like to work in shopify.

http://paydirtgold.com/

 ${\bf Marketplace} \ / \ {\bf Inventory} \ {\bf Management}$ 

This is a marketplace web software which we created for one of our clients. Client has changed the url so don't have exact url. In this we've integrated Amazon MWS API and ebay marketplace.

Nayaindia

It's a news portal like bhaskar.com. Main thing was to show as much data on home page as we can and at the same time we also need to keep the website speed in our mind. If website goes slow then our client can loose users. So you can say this was also a good project for me to manage.

http://nayaindia.com/

EDUCATION

#### Master of Computer Application (MCA)

IGNOU, New Delhi

- Two Years Integrated Masters Program
- Masters program includes Computer Architecture, Computer Organization, Artificial Intelligence, Networking and much more.

## Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA)

2006

2008

IGNOU, New Delhi

- Three Years Bachelor Degree Program
- lacktriangle This includes Theory of computer science, Database management, C, C++ and much more.

SKILLS

Tools & Technologies

- Basecamp, Trello
- PHP, CakePHP, CodeIgniter, Laravel
- MySql, MongoDB
- Wordpress, Woocommerce, Opencart,
  Oscommerce, Shopify
- Qualities
- Jquery, Mootools, AJAX, XML, AWS, Project Execution
- Paypal, CCavenue, 2checkout,
  Authorize.net, Market Data, Stripe,

JSON, HTML5

Leadership skills, integrity
 Excellent writing skills

SDLC Planning & Co-ordination

- Cood
- Infusionsoft, Aweber, Mailchimp
- Good sense of humor